好的，你已经完成了。让我们看看答案。
All right, you're done. Let's look at the solution.
正如我在问题里所说的那样，我们要
As I said in the question, we're going to be
在天气更新功能里的一个forcast fragment组件里工作。
working inside a forecast fragment in the update weather function.
首先，我们需要为我们的alarm receiver新建一个标准的Intent对象。
First, we're going to need to create a standard intent
然后我们把位置查询功能临时添加进来。
for our alarm receiver. We then add our location query
然后打包到一个pendingIntent对象里。
as an extra. We then wrap that in a pending
pendingIntent其实是一种特殊的intent对象。
intent. A pending intent is a special kind of object
它可以让其他应用程序在
that describes an intent. This allows other applications to implement
pendingIntent上使用一些普通Intent
the feature of the original intent that's used to
所包含的特性。其实我们仅仅使用一次PendingIntent，
create the pending intent. We're only going to use this
所以我在这定义了个Flag_One-Shot。
pending intent once, so I set flag one shot.
然后，我们用alarm service设置alarm让他从现在
Then, we get the alarm service and set the alarm
起计时，五秒后触发。但是我们仍然需要
to trigger five seconds from now. But we still
给我们的alarm做点东西。回到Broadcast Receiver，
need for our alarm to do something. Back in the
我们需要发送标准intent对象，
Broadcast Receiver, we need to send the standard intent
然后开始我们的服务，就是这样。让我们试着运行应用程序。
to start our service, and that's it. Let's try running
好的，所以我们已经有了可以停止我们
the app. All right, so now we've got the
的服务的Alarm Manager。
Alarm Manager getting in the way of our service. We
我们点一下刷新。到我们真正看到数据的时候可能至少需要
hit refresh. It'll take us about five more seconds
五秒钟。然后我们等一下。
before we actually see the data now. And there we
一个短暂的小生命诞生，非常简单的alarm。甚至
have it. A very, very simple alarm. Even with
只是在我们不知道的时候就在后台更新了，还有在使用服务的时候，
this updating in the background potentially, and using a service,
我们还可以更高效地使用我们的手机资源。
we could still be more efficient in our use
Rato会告诉我们更多关于他的知识。
of phone resources. Rato can tell us more about that.